Autumn clouds float high in the blue sky.
空が高くなり
秋の雲が浮かぶ
Having had our fill of eating,
食欲旺盛
reading manga, and playing sports this summer,
読書はマンガ
スポーツは体育でご勘弁の俺たちに
we celebrated the arts this fall.
芸術の秋を求める出来事がやってきた
You want me to draw a manga?
俺がマンガ描くの
Y-Yes. Twice a year, the Manga Society...
は　はい　漫研では年に2回
creates an anthology out of manga we've drawn.
皆が描いたマンガを一冊の本にまとめるんです
Really?
あ　そう　そういう部活っぽいこともするの
So they do have some club-like activities...
at the Manga Society.
漫研
Sorry?
はい？
I was enjoying how it was kinda like a do-nothing-and-go-home club.
半帰宅部スタイル　結構好きだったんけどな
But even if I agree to draw a manga,
でも　マンガを描くと言っても
I don't own a beret.
俺ベレー帽持ってないし
You don't need a beret to draw manga.
いえ　ベレー帽は被らなくてもマンガは描けるので
I don't own a striped shirt or have an F in the middle of my name either.
しましまシャツも持ってないし
名前の真ん中にF入ってないし
You don't need any of those.
全部なくても大丈夫です
Please make your manga at least five pages long.
マンガは5ページ以上でお願いします
If you have any questions, just ask.
また何か分からないことがあったら
いつでも聞きに来てください
えっと　誰だっけ
Um, who are you?
I'm a first year. M-Matsushita Ryuunosuke.
一年の松下隆之介です
それじゃ　頑張ってください
A-Anyway, see what you can do.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ     翻译 景寒筱    日校 慧慧
总校 有明の月 喵儿    时间轴 葛蔓     压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Those look great.
あー　いいな
Shun-chan, can I have one?
春ちゃん　一つ頂戴
Go ahead.
どうぞどうぞ
Why do you have those?
What are you, a girl?
何持ってきてんだよ
女子高生か
俺も一ついい
Can I have one, too?
というわけで　今から皆さんにマンガを描いてもらいます
So...
You're all going to draw a manga for me.
Daily Wage Hero
What? B-But why?
ど　どういうわけで？
So that's why you called us here?
っつか集合かけたのそれが理由かよ
そう
Yes.
Isn't this your club activity?
それお前の部活動だろうが
We don't have anything to do with it.
俺たち関係ねえだろう
Well, yeah, but you know...
いや　それがさ　聞いて
俺マンガは読むの専門で
I only read manga.
I've never drawn one before.
描くほうはさっぱりなんだよね
That's why we'll draw in the relay format.
なので　リレー漫画形式で
一人1ページ書き進めてもらって
We'll each draw one page and
combine them to create one story.
五人で一つの作品を完成させたいと思います
Ah, I'll do it!
へー　やるやる！なんか面白そうじゃん　ね
Sounds interesting, doesn't it?
Yes!
はい
I'll hand out the paper.
じゃ　紙配りまーす
俺はパス
I'll pass. I don't draw.
絵は専門外
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't say stuff that'll undermine our teamwork
これから皆で共同作業って時に
when we're about to start a group project.
チームワーク乱すようなこと言うなよな
We don't have any teamwork to undermine.
もともと乱すチームワークがねえだろうが
What should it be about?
どんな話にします
Let's see...
そうだな　スポコン物とかどうや？
How about a sport-com?
A sports comedy?
スポーツコント　描くの難しくない
Don't you think that'd be hard to draw?
スポコンをスポーツ＆根性と解釈できんお前には難しいかもな
Yeah, it might be difficult for you if you can't even figure out
that "sport-com" means a competitive sports story.
I'd prefer a fantasy story with wizards.
僕は魔法使いのファンダジーものがいいな
You would.
そうだね　春自体がちょっとファンダジーだもんね
You're a bit of a fantasy creature, yourself.
要と要のお母さんの愛の記録をラブコメにして描くっていうのは
Why don't we draw a romantic comedy documenting...
the love between Kaname and his mom?
That wouldn't be a comedy.
いや　それはコメディにならないでしょう
It's too taboo.
禁断すぎて
じゃあー
What if someone spotted them?
「悦子は見た」とかは
"At the Tsukahara family, whom she works for, the mother and son are..."
雇われ先の塚原家で母と息子の愛を
Enough!
止めんか
This is getting out of hand.
ごちゃごちゃめんどくせえな
分かりやすく　勇者がいて　魔王とモンスターがいてっていう
Why not stick to...
the simple, classic adventure of a hero,
with a demon king and monsters?
王道の冒険ものでいいじゃねえか
A hero...
勇者？
冒険？
An adventure...
I see!
なるほど　俺たちは大事なジャンルを忘れていた
We've been forgetting about the all-important genre!
The adventure of an ambitious and brave hero is at the core of our youth!
夢と勇気あふれる勇者の冒険こそ
俺たち少年の原点
Okay, let's give it a try!
よーし　ここは一丁　それで行ってみますか
それじゃトップバッター１ページ目は
Well then, first up to bat is Yuutan with the first page!
ゆうたん
Yukki will be second!
2ページ目は　ゆっきー
Shun-chan is third, and I'll go fourth!
3ページ目が春ちゃんで
4ページ目は俺
And Kanamecchi will draw the fifth and final page!
そしてラスト5ページ目が　要っちだん
Isn't this exciting?
わくわくしますね
Kanamecchi, you'll have to carry our efforts over the finish line...
要っち　俺たち全員の思いを背負って
with an emotional conclusion.
感動のフィニッシュ　頼んだぜ
Yeah, I'll carry all of your failures to a pathetically weak finish.
あー　お前ら全員の失敗を背負ってグダグダにフィニッシュしてやるよ
I finished the first page.
1ページ目描けました
待ってました
Finally!
How does it start?
出だしはどんな風になりました
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
Hey, this is good!
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
ってうま
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
Yuuta-kun, I didn't know you could draw!
悠太君絵描くの好きでしたっけ
じゃないけど
I don't, but I grew up in a room overflowing to the rafters with Yuuki's manga.
昔から祐希のマンガであふれた部屋で生活してるし
自然とこうなるよね
It's only natural that this would happen.
No, it's not.
ならねえよ
This is amazing!
すっげえな
Yes!
I swear on this legendary sword!
His costume and sword are awesome!
コスチュームも剣もかっけえ
Hey, who are these two standing next to the hero?
おい　勇者の両脇にいるのは
The country's best spearman and a sex-appeal magician.
この国一番の槍使いとお色気担当魔法使い
It's perfect. This is what boys want!
ばっちりだぜ
少年の原点と言えばこれでしょう
Are you stupid?
あほか
What are you trying to say about innocent boys?
まだ純真無垢な少年の原点にいきなりなんちゅーもの置いてんだよ
But I think it's a great start.
でもスタートとしてはすごくいい感じになりましたね
It is, isn't it?
よーし　この勢いで次はゆっきーもかっこいいの頼んだぜ
All right! Yukki, keep this going and draw something awesome!
I'm done with the second page.
2ページ目描けました
What?
Who's this? What's up with that outfit?
誰これ　何このラフな格好
A convenience store?
Is he going to a convenience store?
コンビニ？　この人これからコンビニ行くの？
What happened between the first and second pages?
1ページ目と2ページ目の間に何が
Yuuta's costume was too hard to draw.
いや　悠太の考えたコスチューム描くの難しくってさ
いろいろ削ってたらこんな感じに
I simplified it and ended up with this.
What did you simplify to have him turn into this?
何を削りゃこんな格好になんだよ
お前経費でも削んねえかぎり
You'd have to "simplify" your costs to make such a low budget hero.
こんな低予算な勇者できあがんねえだろうが
The only thing you worked hard on, the sword, looks even more pitiful.
唯一がんばって描いてもらってる剣が
逆にかわいそうに見えてくるもんね
最高のミスマッチ
They couldn't be more mismatched.
あれ　仲間の二人がいませんけど　どこに
Huh?
His two friends are missing. Where are they?
死んだ
They died.
Already?
はや！
It took all the effort I had just to draw one character.
俺　キャラは一人描くのが限界なんだよね
だから「俺の屍を越えて行け」的な展開にさせてもらった
Thats why I had them say to him "Overcome my death!"
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
This speech bubble doesn't overcome anything!
いや　この吹き出しの位置　越えてねえから
He's totally crushing them under there.
絶対これ仲間踏んづけちゃってるから
You're hopeless, Yukki.
もうダメだ　ゆっきーは
Shun-chan, it's up to you now.
春ちゃんに次を託すよ
O-Okay, I'll do my best!
はい　がんばります
I'm done with the third page!
3ページ目描けました
The hero's eyes are huge!
勇者目でか
In this scene, the hero doesn't give up despite the loss of his friends,
これは仲間を失い　一人になっても決して俯かず
and fixes his gaze on what's ahead.
前だけ見つめるシーンです
Well, with those eyes, he's not just looking ahead—he must have 360° vision!
いいや　前どころか
絶対360度見えてるってこの目
The bitterness of losing his friends to monsters has made made the hero even stronger, it seems.
仲間をモンスターに殺された悔しさが
勇者また一つ強くしたんだね
No, he lost his friends to your artistic skills.
いや　仲間殺したのは祐希の画力だから
It looks like we've got a new character.
A-Are you the hero?!
新キャラも出してみたんです
Exactly what part of this guy in a t-shirt made him seem like a hero to her?
このTシャツ男のどこ見て勇者だと思ったんだよ
She probably spotted his sword with those huge eyes of hers.
剣を見逃さなかったんだろう　目でかいから
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
Help me, Mister Hero!
助けてください　勇者様
My sister... She's been kidnapped by monsters!
妹が　妹がモンスターにさらわれて
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
なんだって
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
What did you say?
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
What did you say!?
大丈夫　きっと私が助けだして見せる
It's all right! I will definitely save her!
It's all right. I'll save her.
Yep, yep. This is it.
A hero has to fight monsters.
勇者と言えばやっぱりモンスターとの激闘
Well? Can you feel the intensity?
どうです　緊迫した空気伝わりました
He wouldn't last long.
秒殺されそう
あと2ページか
Two more pages, huh?
The story's coming along pretty well, isn't it?
なんやかんやここまで結構いい感じに進んでじゃないの
やっと世界を救う展開になりつつあるし
It looks like he's headed towards saving the world.
Well, I don't think the world expects anything from this hero.
まあ　こんな勇者に世界ももう何も期待してないと思うけどね
It's finally my turn, isn't it?
うん　次はついに俺っちの番か
バトルシーンとかもりもり入れてみっかな
Maybe I'll put a little action in by drawing a battle scene.
Asaba-kun.
浅羽君
There's a first-year looking for you.
一年の子が呼んでるよ
H-Hello.
どうも
I came to see how your manuscript is coming along.
原稿の進行状況を伺いに来ました
ど　どうですか
H-How are you doing?
何かわからないこととかないですか
Do you have any questions?
ああ　そうだね　勇者はもう何がしたいのか分かんないよね
Well, yeah... I don't know what the hero wants to do any more.
What?
はい？
Are those the manuscripts of the other club members?
それ　他の人の原稿？
Yes.
はい
あれ　もしかして俺遅れてる
Huh? Am I behind?
No, um...
いえ　ええと
Sorry.
ごめん
I know I'm holding you up, but this might end up way
better than anything a Manga Society member could draw.
しかも待たせるわりにとても漫研とは思えない仕上がりにもなるかもなんだけど
It's fine!
いえ　大丈夫です
You've never really felt like a member of the club.
先輩もともと漫研っぽくないですから
あ　や　えと　悪い意味ではなくて
I mean— Not in a bad way.
H-How should I put it... you like manga and anime, but you don't seem like an otaku at all, unlike me.
なんて言うか
先輩マンガとかアニメとか好きなのに　僕と違って
全然お宅っぽくないっていうか
N-Not to mention how cool you are, so...
かっこいいし
だから　その
Huh?
あれ
I, um... S-Sorry.
なんか　あのう　すみません
いや
It's fine.
What?
何
Nothing. Just got the feeling I got a peek at one of the pages of youth.
いや　ちょっと青春の1ページを覗き見しちゃった気持ちに
The what?
なにそれ
Nevermind, nevermind.
いいじゃないの　いいじゃないの
This is the bittersweetness of our...
こういう甘酸っぱさこそが僕たちの
これだ
That's it!
4ページ目が描けたぞ
I finished the fourth page!
あ　本当ですか
Oh, really?
I'm late, I'm late!
Oh no,
I overslept!
*jog jog*
What? The hero's wearing a school uniform?
I'm late, I'm late!
Oh no,
I overslept!
*jog jog*
勇者学ラン
Forget the adventure!
冒険ものは止めた　こっから違う路線で行く
We'll go with a different theme!
What?
Are you stupid?
あほか　お前
You can't change the genre now!
ここにきてジャンル変更なんかできるか
まあ　今時主人公に食パン加えながら走らせるなんて
Nowadays, having the main character running while eating a piece of toast...
seems plenty adventurous to me.
十分大冒険だけどね
皆　俺たちは一つ大事なジャンルを忘れていた
Everyone, we've forgotten all about an important genre.
それは学園青春もの
That is...
a high-school drama!
勇者の冒険など俺たちが描いたところで
Even if we draw a heroic adventure, it'll be nothing more than fantasy!
しょせんは想像の産物
But the friendship, hard work, and conflict...
だがしかし　思春期に味わう友情　努力　感動
experienced in our adolescence are a reality that we can only draw when we, ourselves, are in our adolescence!
それは現役の俺たちにしか描けないリアルなのだ
Friendship.
友情？
Hard work.
努力
感動？
Conflict.
って　あほか
Are you stupid?
We're not actually living that life, so it's completely unrelated!
現役でも俺たちはそういう青春とまるで無縁だから
敢えてスルーしてたんだろうが
It's okay! Use your imagination!
大丈夫だ　想像力を働かせろ
So, it's imaginary either way.
や　どの道想像じゃないですか
Out of nowhere, a high school girl...
いきなり女子高生
Well, she's kinda like my ideal heroine.
まあ　俺の理想のヒロインってとこかな
Jeez, Hero! You're so late!
This hero's hair looks just like someone else's.
この勇者誰かと髪型が一緒
Sorry, sorry!
Don't get so mad!
Really?
そう　細かいこと気にすんなよ
Don't worry about the details.
What? Already?
ええ　ゴールイン
Why did they get married so quickly?
なんだこのスピード婚
Okay, okay. Kanamecchi, you're next.
はいはい　次は要っちよ
It's the last page!
次でついにラストページ
がんばって
You can do it!
なんかお前らに応援されると腹立つな
Something about your support pisses me off.
ほら　5ページ目描けたぞ
Here. I finished the fifth page.
塚　塚原さん　いきなり舞台が火星に　火星になってんですけど
Tsukahara-san, the setting's suddenly changed to M-Mars...
Kaname-kun, you really are the best at everything.
本当に要君はなんでも一番だな
Best at what?! Sorry I suck at drawing.
なんの一番だよ
悪かったな　ヘタクソで
Come on, Shun, you can do it.
ほら　春　がんばって
If you don't say something supportive, who will?
ここで春がフォローしなきゃ誰がこの絵をフォローするの
Forget about that panel. Keep reading!
そのコマはもういいから　続き見ろよ
すっげぇきれいにまとめてっから
It wraps up really nicely!
たくさんの祝福を受けて結婚した二人
The celebrated newlyweds create a physical embodiment of their love,
その後二人は愛の結晶を授かった
and so the baton of life is passed on—
こうして命のバトンは途切れることなく続いて
Just stop looking at that panel!
っていつまでもそればっか見んな
We've finished all five pages.
これで5ページ全部終了
It was a lot of work, but I'm glad we did it.
いろいろ大変だっけど
よかったね　とりあえず終了して
いやー　結構おもしろかったな　リレーマンガ
Drawing a manga in the relay format was pretty fun.
Let's switch up the order and do it again some time.
また今度順番変えてやろうよ
順番変える前にメンバー変えろ
Change the members before you change the order.
あ　あのう　何かすいません
U-Um, I'm sorry.
For what?
何が
I just figured we might have made something you're not happy with.
いいえ　もしかしたら
祐希君が満足いくようなものにはならなかったんじゃないかと
I wouldn't say that.
いや　そんなことないよ
I could never have drawn five pages by myself.
俺一人じゃ5ページ描き切ることもできなかったし
Thanks for your help.
助かりました
祐希君
Yuuki-kun.
な　ゆっきー　せっかくだから
Yukki, let's go to the faculty office and make copies for all of us.
職員室で俺たちの分もコピー取ろうよ
What are you doing?
なにやっとんじゃ
Our first collaboration ended.
こうして　初めての合作は終わり
Why is the bottom cut off?
なんで下のほう切れてるんですか
A couple of people got really angry.
約2名がすごい勢いでキレたから
As though appalled by our foray into the unfamiliar arts,
俺たちの慣れない芸術の秋
空高く浮かぶ雲が
the high-flying autumn clouds drifted away in boredom.
あきれた様子で流れていった
You And I
僕には憧れのヒーローがいる
There's a hero who I admire.
Most heroes come from a faraway place in the cosmos,
ヒーローは遠い宇宙の彼方からやってくるというけれど
その人は
but he...
You want me to draw a manga?
俺がマンガ描くの
Y-Yes.
は、はい
そ　それじゃ　がんばってください
A-Anyway, see what you can do.
°
Senpai and I
Manga Society
Did you ask him to do it?
頼んできてくれた
Yes.
はい
Well?
He listened earnestly to what I had to say.
すごく真剣に受け止めてくれて
たぶん描いてくれるんじゃないかと
I think he'll do it.
Really?
That's amazing!
本当？　すごい　売れるかも
This might actually sell.
It might even sell out.
即完売するかもな
I wonder what he'll draw?
どんなの描いてくれるんですかね
Probably a sports story.
やっぱスポコンじゃない
The protagonist will join the Basketball Club,
バスケ部とかに入部して
make friends,
仲間ができて
塚原君みたいな男子と
and with a boy like Tsukahara-kun...
I wanna read it now!
早く読みたい
If it sells, I guess.
まあ　売れればありだよな
I know, right?
だね
He's not that kind of a hero.
そういうヒーローじゃ
All right! I'm going make a manga for the club about Yuuki-senpai.
決めた
部活動のマンガ
僕は祐希先輩の話を描こう
どんなのがいいかな
I wonder what I should write. A hero is...
やっぱりヒーローって言ったら
The cake is ours!
ケーキは皆いただいた
Stop!
そこまでだ
What?
Team Skull, I won't let you do as you please with the Earth!
どくろ軍団　この地球はお前たちの好きにはさせない
変身
Transform!
Susume ima!
Go forward now!
進め　今
叫べ　ほら
Sakebe hora!
Come on, shout!
Ao chikyuu wo mamoru tame,
To defend this blue Earth,
Hero Blue!
ヒーローブルー
青い地球を守るため
Kibou no hikari wo terasu tame,
To shine the light of hope,
希望の光を照らすため
Hero Yellow!
ヒーローイエロー
Go! Go! Bokura no Homa Ranger!
Go! Go! Our Homa Rangers!
ゴー　ゴー　僕らはホマレンジャー
Hero Black!
ヒーローブラック
Hero Pink!
ヒーローピンク
Kyou wo dokoka de Homa Ranger
The Homu Rangers are somewhere out there today
今日も　どこかでホマレンジャー
Hero Red!
ヒーローレッド
Together, we are...
5人合わせて
Homa Ranger!
ホマレンジャー
High School Fighting Homa Rangers!
高校戦隊ホマレンジャー
So cool.
かっこいい
これだこれ
That's what I'll write.
かっこよくポーズ決めて　5人は
The five of them pose together, and...
Together, we are...
5人合わせて
高校戦隊穂稀勇者
High School Fighting Homa Rangers!
Why are you the only one wearing your school uniform?
って何がお前一人だけ制服着てんだ
I can't pull off full-body tights.
だって俺全身タイツとかかなり無理なんだけど
These aren't full-body tights!
全身タイツじゃねえ
いやあ　皆よく着たよね
I'm surprised you guys wore them.
これからもぜひテレビの前のちびっこたちに
Please continue teaching the kids...
in front of the TV the true meaning of bravery.
本当の勇気とは何かを伝え続けていって下さい
勇気とかいうな
Don't call it "bravery"!
なんかめちゃめちゃ恥ずかしくなって来たじゃねえか
Th-This is getting really embarrassing!
Stop it!
止めてください
We're a team. We can't afford to fight now!
今は仲間同士争ってる場合じゃありません
You're right.
そうだった
All right, everyone!
よし　皆
Let's work together to defeat our enemies!
力を合わせて　敵を倒すぞ
You have to fight, too!
お前も戦え
M-Maybe I'll try something else.
やっぱり違う話にしようかな
他に祐希先輩に似合いそうなものは
What else would suit Yuuki-senpai?
Old man, I'm taking this girl until you pay your debts.
そんじゃあおやじ　この娘借金の形にもらってくぜ
Dad!
おとっつあん
Oshun!
お春
Hold it right there.
待ちな
You're the child-toting samurai!
お前は
子連れ侍
If you must take someone...
連れて行くなら
Take him.
こっちをお願いします
もう本当に困ってたんだよ
He's just been a pain in the neck.
He's too heavy to take anywhere.
どこ行くにもいちいち重くってさ
I can't come up with anything good.
なかなかうまく描けないな
す　すみません
S-Sorry.
先輩
Senpai!
ちょうどよかった　原稿のことなんだけど
Oh, perfect.
I don't think I'll be done with my manuscript any time soon.
まだ時間がかかりそうで
Oh, that's fine.
いえ　大丈夫です
僕もまだ全然で
I'm not close to finishing at all.
そうなんなの
Really?
ダメじゃん　松下君
That's no good, Matsushita-kun.
じゃ　がんばってね
You can do it.
やっぱり浅羽先輩かっこいいよね
Asaba-senpai is so cool!
Yuuta-senpai's so great,
but Yuuki-senpai has like, a dark side.
悠太先輩もすごくすてきだけど
祐希先輩は影があるっていうか
His lone wolf attitude is so cool.
一匹狼っぽいところがいいよね
That's it!
これだ
You again, Asaba?
またお前か　浅羽
If you get in trouble again, you'll be expelled!
次問題起こしたら　退学だからな
Please Adopt Me
お前も一人なんだな
You're alone, too.
Stop it!
よせって
What do you want?
なんだ　てめー
余計なことすんじゃ…
What do you think you're...
I saw a lonely puppy shivering in the rain.
子犬が寂しそうに震えてたから
Yes!
This is great.
これすごくいい
I'll go with this.
この路線で行こう
I can't agree to this.
僕には賛成できないな
君みたいな女性に
A girl like you isn't suited to be with a brute like Asaba.
浅羽のような野蛮人が釣り合うとは思えない
Stop it, Tsukahara-kun!
やめて　塚原君　祐希はそんな人じゃないわ
Yuuki's not that kind of person.
彼のこと悪く言わないで
Don't say bad things about him!
It seems as if you took care of our Mon recently.
この間うちのもんを可愛がってくれたようだな
I've come to thank you.
礼をしにきてやったぜ
Boss, get him!
おやびん　やっちまってくだせえ
Looks like you've got a cutie with you today.
今日は可愛い子連れてるじゃねえか
ちょっとこっちこいよ
Come here.
Don't touch my girl.
俺の女に触んじゃねえよ
Stop it!
もうやめて
お願い
Please! I don't want to see you get hurt any more.
私これ以上祐希が傷つくの見たくない
Let go, Matsuoka.
放せ　松岡
No.
いや
Let go.
放せ
No!
いや
Let go!
放せ
No!
いや
Let go!
放せ
There's an anime at five I want to watch.
5時から見たいアニメが
What?
That's weird. Why can't I draw anything?
おかしいな　なんでこんなに描けないんだろう
もしかして
Could it be...
Hello.
どうも
Senpai, what are you doing here?
先輩
こんなところで何してるんですか
いや　クラスのメガネ君をちょっと怒らせっちゃってね
I pissed off my class's Four-eyes-kun.
I'm hiding from him.
今逃げてるとこ
What are you actually doing?
本当に何してるんですか
Could it be that Yuuki-senpai isn't heroic at all?
もしかして　祐希先輩ってそんなにヒーローっぽくない
だからいつもあんな展開に
Is that why my stories keep turning out that way?
危ない
Watch out!
Thank you, Senpai!
先輩　ありがとうございます
Excuse me. Can we have our ball back, please?
すいません　ボール取ってください
There's a hero I admire.
僕には憧れのヒーローがいる
Most heroes come from a faraway place in the cosmos,
ヒーローは遠い宇宙の彼方からやってくるというけれど
but he's not from a place that far away.
その人はそんな遠くからはるばるやってこない
Probably because it'd be too much effort.
たぶんめんどくさいから
だけどそれでもやっぱり僕はどんなヒーローより
But I still think he's greater than any hero.
かっこういいと思ってしまうのだ
Let me see your manga when you're done with it, Matsushita-kun.
マンガ描けたら見せてね
松下君
Yes!
はい
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Budget Review
次回　ネイキッドキング
"Next time: Naked King."